<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Lukas' Blog</title>
    <description>About the things I make</description>
    <link>https://blog.cvguy.de</link>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.cvguy.de/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>The Super Nintendo RetroPie Casemod</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Ok, this is a project that probably has been done many times already, but I needed to do this to resolve a little childhood trauma.
I had a Game Boy but my parents never allowed me to have a Super Nintendo.
I guess that is what you get when you spend too much time with your handheld console but not enough time with your homework.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 17:27:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.cvguy.de/2020/the-supernintendo-retropi-casemod/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.cvguy.de/2020/the-supernintendo-retropi-casemod/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Distinguishing Cats from Dogs with Deeplearning4j, Kotlin and the VGG16 model</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;The first task in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fast.ai/&quot;&gt;fast.ai&lt;/a&gt; course is to enter a compitition on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kaggle.com/c/dogs-vs-cats&quot;&gt;Kaggle&lt;/a&gt;.
The competitions goal is to successfully distinguish between cat and dog images.
I didn’t go so far to submit my result to Kaggle, but instead, I gave myself the challenge to solve the problem within a completely different technology stack rather than using the one from the course.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:25:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.cvguy.de/2017/using-deeplearning4j-to-distinguish-between-cats-and-dogs/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.cvguy.de/2017/using-deeplearning4j-to-distinguish-between-cats-and-dogs/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Setting up the fast.ai deep learning course on OSX with Anaconda</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;So I decided to give a try to the free deep learning course published on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fast.ai/&quot;&gt;fast.ai&lt;/a&gt;.
The first lesson was not too difficult for me as half on it was about setting up things.
The other half were mostly things I already knew about deep learning, but it was refreshing to see how things are actually done with real code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 22:22:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.cvguy.de/2017/fast-ai-course-on-macmini/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.cvguy.de/2017/fast-ai-course-on-macmini/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Building a R2D2 Themed Bluetooth Speaker</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;My girlfriend brought &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.co.jp/search?q=r2d2+popcorn+bucket&amp;amp;tbm=isch&quot;&gt;a R2D2 shaped popcorn bucket&lt;/a&gt; from Tokyo Disneyland the other day.
Turns out that it’s pretty much useless, once the popcorn is gone… so I took my freedom to build something out of it.
And all I needed were some tools and a Raspberry Pi 3.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 23:12:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.cvguy.de/2017/building-a-r2d2-themed-bluetooth-speaker/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.cvguy.de/2017/building-a-r2d2-themed-bluetooth-speaker/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making Bluetooth Audio Work Properly on the Raspberry Pi 3</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;The Raspberry Pi 3 ships with a Bluetooth chip which is awesome.
It can be used for many purposes but the first thing that comes into my mind is to transform it into a portable speaker.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 14:32:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.cvguy.de/2017/creating-a-blootooth-speaker-with-raspberrypi-3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.cvguy.de/2017/creating-a-blootooth-speaker-with-raspberrypi-3/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Streaming Geoblocked Contents without VPN</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;So the UEFA Euro cup 2016 is on and I am sitting here in Tokyo wanting to watch the games.
I could get cable or go to sport bars.
Getting cable just for the games is not worth the money and hanging around in bars at night (the games will show from around 11pm to 5am here) is not a favorable option as well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 15:22:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>https://blog.cvguy.de/2016/streaming-geoblocked-contents-without-vpn/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.cvguy.de/2016/streaming-geoblocked-contents-without-vpn/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>